sawlive.tv 2019-06-24

# Stream&Watch

SawLive.tv ("Stream&Watch", "we" or "us") respects and takes the privacy of the visitors, users and members of its website (www.SawLive.tv) (the "Website") very seriously. We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive and collect on the Website. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the provisions of the Terms of Use, and your use of the Website and any personal information you provide us with, are subject to the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. BY USING THE WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF USE AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY, REGARDLESS OF YOUR FAILURE TO READ THEM. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy or with the Terms of Use, please do not use the Website. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in the [Terms of Use](http://sawlive.tv/terms "Terms of Use"). 

You should be aware that when you share or broadcast personal information in public areas of the Website, such as channels and chat rooms, this information becomes publicly available and can be seen, used and gathered by others, and therefore is not subject to this Privacy Policy. We urge you to exercise good judgment when sharing personal information in these forums. Any User Generated Content may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

**_What Information does Stream &Watch Collects and for what purpose?_**

Our main goals in collecting information are to provide and improve the Website and its services, and to administer the membership of registered users. 

_Anonymous Information about visits in the Website_ \- When you visit the Website (whether as a member or as a visitor), information about your visit (such as how you navigate the site) may be collected and stored. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser and platform type, the length of your visit, the date and time of your visit, the pages you viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the websites you visit before and after leaving the Website. It does not include any personally identifiable information such as your name, e-mail address or telephone number. 

We use this information mainly to monitor and analyze the aggregate use of the Website and its services, and for the Website's technical administration. As mentioned above, we may aggregate such data (alone or with Personal Information) in order to better design the Website and services. 

_Cookies_ \- Like many other websites, we use "cookies" to collect information and to tailor the Website to the needs and interests of its members and visitors. A cookie is a small entry-in text file that is transferred from the Website's servers to your computer's hard drive, and uniquely identifies your browser. Cookies can only be read by the server that sent them to you, and cannot read data from your hard drive. The Website uses two types of Cookies for two purposes: (1) Persistent cookies that remain on your hard drive after you close your browser, and are used to save some information about you and your preferences (e.g. your registration ID) for future visits to the Website. (2) Session cookies that are temporary and are deleted from your hard drive after you close your browser. 

We use cookies to: (1) remember some information (e.g. registration ID) so that you will not have to re-enter it during each visit to the Website; (2) provide you with custom, personalized content and information; (3) monitor the effectiveness of marketing campaigns; and (4) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc. 

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you before accepting a cookie. However, you may not be able to access some areas, or use some functionalities of the Website, which require cookies. 

**_Links to other websites and Advertisements_**

The Website may contain links to third party websites and advertisements. If you choose to visit such linked websites or advertisements, by clicking on a link or a banner, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that such links and advertisements are posted and presented on the Website is not an endorsement or representation of any kind, of those websites or their privacy policies and practices. We assume no responsibility in any way for the privacy policies and practices of other websites and encourage you to review the privacy policies of those linked websites before using them. 

We may use third-parties, known as ad-servers, to serve and target advertisements, promotions and other marketing messages, in connection with the Website. Such third parties may use technologies (such as cookies) to monitor the effectiveness of marketing campaigns. We do not control the activities of such third parties, assume no responsibility in any way for their privacy policies and practices, and encourage you to review their privacy policies. We do not provide any such third-parties with any Personal Information, without your consent. However, you should be aware that your response to certain advertisements or campaigns, targeted at specific audiences, may reveal personal information about yourself (such as age or area of residence). Such third parties may also collect and use non-identifying information about your usage of the Website. 

**_Children_**

This Website is not directed to and intended for minors under 13 and does not knowingly collect Personal Information and other types of information about minors. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use this Website. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information, he or she should contact using the contact us form. 

**_Amendments of this Privacy Policy_**

Stream&Watch reserves the right to amend, update or modify, at any time, this Privacy Policy without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any amendments. Such amendments, updates and modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting them on the Website. Your use of the Website following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. We recommend that you check the Website periodically for any such amendments to this Privacy Policy. We further recommend that you print a copy of this Privacy Policy for future reference. 

If you have any questions or comments with regard to this Privacy Policy, your Personal Information or any other related issue, please contact us at [[email protected]](http://sawlive.tv/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
